What if I didn't make a big mistake before?
What's going on between you and Liam?
Nothing is going on between us.
I don't know what can happen
because of your choice.
- You're the one I love.
- I finally found you.
Our meeting wasn't an accident.
Every time someone uses this typewriter,
I remember my past, my life story,
and the curse of this typewriter.
Filipinos see him as a traitor.
And because of the fury
and the desire to be loved...
You will pay for all your sins.
Sabel!
Megan?
Miss Joyce.
Megan.
There's something I need to tell you.
The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair...
I manage that account.
Sorry.
That was you?
You are the one who posted
defamatory things about me?
About Liam and me?
Sorry, Miss Joyce.
I needed the money.
I'm the only one who supports my child.
We don't always have projects.
You can slap me or hurt me, Miss Joyce.
If you want to do it, it's okay.
I'm really sorry.
I'm ashamed of what I did.
I'm so sorry, Miss Joyce.
Who's paying you?
Who told you to do this?
It's Via.
Miss Joyce, I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Please have mercy on me.
My son will be left alone.
It hurts to hear this from you, Megan.
I'm hurting because I treat you as family.
I'm not surprised why Via did that to me.
I can only think of one way...
to get Via punished.
You're so cowardly, Hans. So coward!
You're a coward.
You're just a stupid attorney,
who can't even defend himself.
Via, Via.
Let's go home. I'm going home.
Go on.
Everyone leaves me anyway.
Come on. I'll drive you home. Let's go.
No.
Let's go, Via.
- Via!
- I said no!
- Where are you taking me?
- Perverts are not allowed here!
Don't ever come back.
We've arrived in Segunda!
This is Lando, my most trusted gunman.
Ouch!
It's nothing.
There's no wound.
What was it that I saw? Did I die?
What's the meaning of that?
What does Liam have to do with all these?
That was deep.
I will turn myself in, Mom.
What?
Why?
Mom...
I need to pay for all the crimes I committed.
And...
this is the only way to stop
Congressman Ramon's evil doings.
Even Lando and...
Vergil.
No matter what happens...
my love for you will never change, my son.
I love you, Mom.
Intoy.
Do you have a place to stay?
You better stay here with the typewriter.
So, at least no one else can use it.
You know how powerful that typewriter is.
We don't know what can happen
if it gets in the hands of the wrong people.
Typewriter...
Powerful?
They seem to have lost it.
Hello, friends!
This is your trusted showbiz authority.
The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair.
But I realized it's also wrong
to hide using a secret identity.
The only thing it does for me
is to escape accountability.
That's why tonight,
I am going to reveal who I really am.
My friends,
The Girl with the Periwinkle hair,
is no other than me, Victoria dela Peña.
Megan!
Megan, get out of there!
What are you posting online?
Megan!
Are you looking for Megan?
She left last night with her kid.
They were in a hurry.
She left?
Where did they go?
I don't know.
Isn't that Victoria dela Peña?
That's Via.
The one who confessed she's
The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair.
She's the one spreading rumors
about celebrities.
Excuse you.
That's not me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Where do you think are you going?
- Oh my God!
- Hey, hey!
- What are you doing?
- You deserve this!
Don't touch me!
Get out of here!
Don't ever come back!
We need to talk about Joyce.
Why?
What do you know?
What did Via tell you?
This is not about Via, Hans.
This is about Joyce.
I have to do something important,
and I want you to protect her.
So she won't get involved.
Mr. Herrera,
do you understand that
this is a serious accusation
against the Senate candidate,
Congressman dela Peña?
I'm willing to go to jail
to pay for all my crimes.
I want to make all the culprits pay.
- Sir, question.
- Hold on.
- We're going to start.
- I will just ask questions.
- Sir?
- Go over there for now.
Okay, okay.
Sir, please sit down.
All the money that is being laundered
in Casa Fuerte
comes from the illegal businesses
of Congressman Ramon dela Peña,
under my authorization.
We also collect dirty money
from different parts of the country.
We invest it in Casa Fuerte to launder it.
I run the company as CEO.
And the president of the company,
your father, Danilo Herrera?
He doesn't know anything about this.
[Seal of the President of the Philippines]
Mr. President,
Congressman Ramon dela Peña is here.
Let him in.
My half-brother Vergil Herrera
took over my position in Casa Fuerte.
Mr. President,
I thought this is an intimate meeting.
He also knows
all the illegal dealings
of Congressman Ramon,
which were executed
by his right-hand man, Lando.
Lando Nakpil.
- We also collect...
- Go on.
Leave us alone for now.
That comes from different parts
of the country.
Then, we invest it in Casa Fuerte
to launder it.
Mr. President, I assure you that he's lying.
That Liam Herrera is from my rival's camp.
Who's the rival you're referring to,
Congressman dela Peña?
Those that I defeated in my district
who wanted to smear my reputation
because I'm doing well
in the senatorial surveys.
The House Ethics Committee
is set to open an investigation.
Ethics Committee?
Wait, Mr. Speaker.
Did you check if Liam is telling the truth?
Mr. President, are you going to believe...
Stop it, Ramon!
I believe that you serve
the people with honesty.
I also believe that you are
popular among the masses,
that's why you were included
in the senatorial slate.
But it turns out,
you are one who can bring the party down.
Mr. President, hear me out.
Let the court decide.
Ramon, listen carefully.
Once all the accusations against you
are proven to be true,
I will make sure you'll go to jail.
Ramon, I also regret to inform you
that you're no longer a member of the party.
You can still pursue
your senatorial aspiration,
but you can't get any endorsement or support
from the party
or the President.
You'll regret this.
Stop!
This way!
Liam is such a pest. He's a troublemaker.
Dad.
I need your help.
Help?
What is it, my dear daughter?
Megan has exposed me
as The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair.
They're talking about me online.
People are talking too much.
They're already ruining my image.
Isn't it true?
Do you think I still
have time to worry about you?
Do you know what happened earlier?
The President of the Philippines
kicked me out of the party!
My political career is ruined.
And you want me to solve
that worthless Periwinkle thing?
Your boyfriend, Liam,
has caused my downfall.
You brought that bad luck to our family, Via.
He has too many exposés about me.
Why?
Isn't it true?
Darn it!
Don't use my words against me!
Just admit it, Dad.
We both have rotten personalities.
You pretend to be a good person
in front of others.
If I'm plastic, then you're rubber.
We're both going to burn in hell.
But you are worse than I am.
That's enough.
Go ahead!
I'm already numb, Dad.
You've killed me long ago.
- Hans.
- Aunt Tess.
What does this mean?
You have to come with us.
Liam asked me to take you to a safe house.
Intoy isn't here yet.
Who's Intoy?
He's the man staying with us.
I'm sorry, Aunt Tess. We need to leave now.
Do we really need to hide from Ramon
like we are rats?
He will not stop until he gets back at Liam
and at everyone dear to him,
while he's still in power.
Okay.
But please come back for Intoy, okay?
We will.
Borj, thank you.
You even brought me food.
It's nothing, Boss Bro.
Anything for you.
Deedee and Leroy want to say hi to you.
They got a new project
in a rising film company.
Why are you so quiet?
I'm not used to seeing you like that.
Nothing, Boss Bro.
I'm just shocked at what happened.
I feel like I didn't give my all.
I've been your assistant for years,
but I learned only now
about your dirty business.
If I only knew, I could have stopped you.
Borj, you did nothing wrong.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Borj.
Boss Bro, you sound like...
you're saying goodbye.
I'm just going on a vacation.
But I think it's going to be a long one.
Seriously, Borj, thank you for your loyalty.
Thank you for the friendship.
Promise me, Borj...
that no matter what happens,
you won't end up like me.
Work decently.
Boss Bro.
I should thank you.
Thank you for...
trusting me.
Borj, always take care.
I'm worried that you will get involved too,
given Congressman Ramon's temper.
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself, Boss Bro.
Go on and eat.
What's this?
Betute.
Wow.
Liam has listed your name
for the protection program
to keep you safe
from the people he will identify.
How long do we stay here
in the safe house, Ma'am?
There's no definite time.
But you have to stay here
until the situation settles down.
Madam policewoman, thank you.
I don't want to die young
because I still want to get married.
Hello, Jana.
Do you know what's the latest?
My goodness! Via and his father,
Congressman Ramon,
they are spreading evil!
Jana, you know what to do.
Make this issue explosive.
Ruin Via.
She has no one to take after
than her darn father.
Okay. Very good.
Do it.
You didn't forget about me.
Ginataang betute.
This is good!
Liam.
Sir.
Dad.
Dad, I'm sorry.
- No...
- I'm sorry.
I should apologize to you.
I have a lot of shortcomings.
I turned a blind eye on Ramon.
Dad.
Dad, you did nothing wrong.
This all started with me.
Vergil just continued it.
But you...
you're innocent.
This is your fault, Liam.
You're inconsiderate.
If you want to go to jail, just do so!
- Why did you have to get me involved?
- You did worse than me, Vergil.
You think I don't know
you were at the orphanage when Sep died?
- Watch your...
- Shut up!
The kid asked you for help
when he was having a heart attack.
But what did you do?
You walked away
like you didn't see or hear anything!
You, monster!
You let an innocent kid die!
Take back what you said!
- That's enough!
- Stop!
Is that true?
Dad...
That's enough!
Stop it! You can't make a scene here!
You're evil!
I raised a demon!
Stop! You can't cause trouble here!
Put them back in the cell.
I thought this place was safe.
But there is someone here
who's making it otherwise.
Is there a problem, Joanne?
Yes, a big problem.
Because all along,
my suspicions about your son were right.
Bad news.
He can't be trusted.
What do we care about your family's mess?
I didn't do anything wrong
to Congressman Ramon!
My son is just doing the right thing.
No one is forcing you to stay
if you don't want to be here.
You can leave if you want.
Yes. I'm leaving.
That's enough, Joanne!
I don't care about your son's crimes!
What I hate the most is
being bothered by someone else's mess!
I can afford my own security.
Odet, Joyce, let's go.
Oh, Madam! Madam!
What about my private security?
I don't want to get kidnapped.
Do you think someone
will take interest in you?
Excuse me.
Mom, let's be reasonable.
Joyce is right, Aunt Joanne.
We don't know what can happen.
This safe house is too small for Tess and me.
Okay, let's do this.
I will let you go back to your house.
But you will be under police surveillance
until you get your own security detail.
I'm telling you...
it's dangerous to stay in your house.
Okay, fine.
Where's my room?
Let's go.
See? She's scared.
What did you say?
- Oh, nothing.
- Let's go!
I said, let's go.
Tess?
Liam?
The typewriter!
Via.
How could you?
After everything that my dad did for you.
Via, I'm sorry.
But maybe it's time...
to do what's right.
Do what's right?
Is it right to betray
your girlfriend's father?
We have to stop this.
What?
Via, I tried.
I tried to love you. Believe me.
Tried?
Tell me the truth.
Did you really love me?
I know how much you loved me.
And I will never forget that.
So I'm sorry, Via.
Sorry?
You are sorry, Liam? That's all I get?
An apology?
There's a special place in hell
for the both of you.
You deserve to be together.
Do you think I will see you differently
just because you owned up to your mistakes?
Whether you see me differently or not,
Joyce...
it doesn't matter.
I just...
want to rectify all my mistakes.
I don't want anyone else to suffer
because of my wrong decisions.
I wish you have thought
about that before, Liam.
You should have thought about it
before you ruined my life.
Turning yourself in won't fix
all the trouble you caused.
Remember that.
You're no different from
Ramon dela Peña, Vergil, Via...
You are all the same!
You all ruined my life!
You are no different from them.
You all killed Sep!
- You made my father blind!
- Joyce...
I was just a puppet at Casa Fuerte.
I had nothing to do
with Uncle Edmond's blindness
nor with Sep's death.
The only wrong I did
was I used the typewriter.
Stop it! Enough, please. Stop!
Don't blame the typewriter.
Don't blame all your mistakes on a fantasy.
If it's true that these
are all the typewriter's fault,
you shouldn't have...
You shouldn't have
brought me back to life!
You should have just let me die!
I will ask again.
What secret does the typewriter have?
What?
You can do everything you want with me.
You can kill me if you want!
But I will never die!
You may not die,
but that doesn't mean you don't get hurt.
So? Does it hurt?
Does it hurt?
With that look right now,
you just might wish
that you are not immortal...
That you'd rather die!
Is that right?
What did you and Liam talk about?
I have no obligation to tell you.
Let me get it straight.
Are you mad at me because
you found out that I'm the person
behind The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair?
Why, though?
Everything I said was true, anyway.
Even the thing about your junkie father.
It's all true, Joyce.
All the secrets I revealed...
you had it coming your way.
You and your whole family!
Remember this, Joyce.
No secret remains hidden.
How?
How can I make you pay?
For making my father blind?
Who told you that, Joyce?
Was it Liam?
Who told you that?
You said so yourself.
No secret remains hidden.
Be prepared to pay for all your sins.
How does the darn typewriter work?
I won't tell you anything!
You're stubborn.
If you're not worth anything,
I should kill Liam instead.
Or Tess...
Don't.
Don't!
Don't do that! Don't!
Fine.
You can change past events...
Past events in your life...
If you rewrite it using the typewriter.
It's like a genie...
Right, like a genie.
That's it?
Nothing more? Is that it?
You animal!
Why didn't I realize this soon?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's why I feel like I died
but came back to life.
You should die!
The typewriter can bring
the dead back to life?
Wow.
You monster! Don't take it away!
You're the one who brought tragedy
into this family.
It happens again and again.
And it all started...
when you cheated on mom.
You had an affair.
I made a mistake.
But she didn't give me a second chance.
I begged her, but... she won't hear me out.
So from then on,
I hate begging for second chances.
So it is true.
Mom took her own life...
because of you.
I lost my mom because of you.
When Mom died,
I thought, finally,
since it's just the two of us,
I would feel your presence.
But I was wrong.
You know what hurts me, Dad?
I wasn't enough reason for you to fight...
and strive to become a good person
because you still have a child.
What for?
Who are you?
Are you her?
Did I do you wrong?
You're just my child.
I won't change just for you.
You have nothing else in your mind
aside from your obsession with Liam.
If there's something
I'll ask for forgiveness,
it will be what's going to happen tonight.
Because I will kill Liam.
No, Dad.
No. No, Dad, no!
No, don't do that, please!
- Take it back! That's not true!
- Get off me!
Dad, don't, please! Please. Dad...
Not Liam, please.
Dad, not Liam!
Dad!
I need your help right now.
Hey, where are you taking me?
Just chill, kid.
Your outfit suits the event tonight.
Take him.
Hans, I want to ask your forgiveness...
For all the time that I made you wait.
Now, you're still here...
You're still waiting for me. I'm sorry.
Maybe...
like in the films...
We're not meant to be together in the end.
I'll cherish everything that we shared.
You're such a good person.
I want to choose you, but...
You don't have to force yourself.
What's in your heart is all that matters.
Don't worry if you're
going to hurt other people.
Joyce, what's important is for you
to be happy.
I'll be okay with that.
I don't want you to regret
your decision someday.
I don't want that.
[Ms. Joyce, you instructed me
to keep an eye on Mr. Herrera.]
[He was brought to this address:
Pulang Buhangin]
I'm glad you came.
What's that?
Long story.
Come with me.
Dad will kill Liam.
Where can they possibly go?
I'll stay out of that, Via.
That's between you and your dad.
Are you serious?
How much?
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much...
for everything.
You deserve to be happy.
You should be free.
Maybe in this lifetime,
we're not meant for each other.
Dad!
I won't let Dad kill you.
We'll be together. This is what I want.
This is my wish.
Dex!
- Joyce.
- Liam is my husband.
Liam and Via suddenly disappeared.
They're looking for them now.
What?
I was badly injured because of the gunshot.
Why did you take the bullet for me?
I don't know, either.
All I know is, I love you.
Mom.